#document_id:TheQuarterlyMusicalMagazineAndReview__1825-025.txt_2407
#document_date:1825
#sent_text:Ferri, Matteucci, and Guadagni, were knighted; Farinelli was presented with the cross of Calatrava, in Spain, where, under his direction and management were revived, in theatrical spectacles, all the magnificence and good taste of ancient Athens.
Ferri	B-person	Q80474	Ferri	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
Matteucci	B-person	NIL	Matteucci	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
Guadagni	B-person	Q3094278	Guadagni	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
were	O	_	be	AUX
knighted	O	_	knight	VERB
;	O	_	;	PUNCT
Farinelli	B-person	Q223744	Farinelli	PROPN
was	O	_	be	AUX
presented	O	_	present	VERB
with	O	_	with	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
cross	B-organization	Q756910	cross	NOUN
of	I-organization	Q756910	of	ADP
Calatrava	I-organization	Q756910	Calatrava	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
in	O	_	in	ADP
Spain	B-country	Q29	Spain	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
where	O	_	where	SCONJ
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
under	O	_	under	ADP
his	O	_	his	PRON
direction	O	_	direction	NOUN
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
management	O	_	management	NOUN
were	O	_	be	AUX
revived	O	_	revive	VERB
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
in	O	_	in	ADP
theatrical	O	_	theatrical	ADJ
spectacles	O	_	spectacle	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
all	O	_	all	DET
the	O	_	the	DET
magnificence	O	_	magnificence	NOUN
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
good	O	_	good	ADJ
taste	O	_	taste	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
ancient	O	_	ancient	ADJ
Athens	B-city	Q1524	Athens	PROPN
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
