#document_id:TheHarmonicon__1824-016.txt_1256
#document_date:1824
#sent_text:(Printed for G. and W. B. Whittaker, dve Maria Lune; and Clementi and Co., Cheapside.)
(	O	_	(	PUNCT
Printed	O	_	print	VERB
for	O	_	for	ADP
G.	O	_	G.	PROPN
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
W.	O	_	W.	PROPN
B.	O	_	B.	PROPN
Whittaker	O	_	Whittaker	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
dve	O	_	dve	X
Maria	B-person	NIL	Maria	PROPN
Lune	I-person	NIL	Lune	PROPN
;	O	_	;	PUNCT
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
Clementi	B-company	NIL	Clementi	PROPN
and	I-company	NIL	and	CCONJ
Co.	I-company	NIL	Co.	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
Cheapside	O	_	Cheapside	PROPN
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
)	O	_	)	PUNCT
