#document_id:TheMusicalWorld__1843-038.txt_630
#document_date:1843
#sent_text:Miss Bassano studied three years in the Royal Academy of Music, where Miss Bassano ranks high in the estimation both of masters and students.
Miss	B-person	Q1872112	Miss	PROPN
Bassano	I-person	Q1872112	Bassano	PROPN
studied	O	_	study	VERB
three	O	_	three	NUM
years	O	_	year	NOUN
in	O	_	in	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Royal	B-organization	Q1144673	Royal	PROPN
Academy	I-organization	Q1144673	Academy	PROPN
of	I-organization	Q1144673	of	ADP
Music	I-organization	Q1144673	Music	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
where	O	_	where	SCONJ
Miss	B-person	Q1872112	Miss	PROPN
Bassano	I-person	Q1872112	Bassano	PROPN
ranks	O	_	rank	VERB
high	O	_	high	ADV
in	O	_	in	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
estimation	O	_	estimation	NOUN
both	O	_	both	CCONJ
of	O	_	of	ADP
masters	O	_	master	NOUN
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
students	O	_	student	NOUN
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
