#document_id:TheQuarterlyMusicalMagazineAndReview__1826-029.txt_1038
#document_date:1826
#sent_text:Sir W. Jones, in his Catalogue of Manuscripts, deposited in the library of the Royal Society, gives us the names of some treatises in the Hindustanee language, which of course have never been translated. .
Sir	B-person	Q273969	Sir	PROPN
W.	I-person	Q273969	W.	PROPN
Jones	I-person	Q273969	Jones	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
in	O	_	in	ADP
his	O	_	his	PRON
Catalogue	B-publication	NIL	catalogue	NOUN
of	I-publication	NIL	of	ADP
Manuscripts	I-publication	NIL	Manuscripts	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
deposited	O	_	deposit	VERB
in	O	_	in	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
library	O	_	library	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Royal	B-organization	Q123885	Royal	PROPN
Society	I-organization	Q123885	Society	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
gives	O	_	give	VERB
us	O	_	we	PRON
the	O	_	the	DET
names	O	_	name	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
some	O	_	some	DET
treatises	O	_	treatise	NOUN
in	O	_	in	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Hindustanee	B-language	Q11051	hindustanee	ADJ
language	O	_	language	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
which	O	_	which	PRON
of	O	_	of	ADP
course	O	_	course	NOUN
have	O	_	have	AUX
never	O	_	never	ADV
been	O	_	be	AUX
translated	O	_	translate	VERB
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
