#document_id:TheHarmonicon__1832-012.txt_1882
#document_date:1832
#sent_text:On the 19th September, a concert was given by the pupils of the Conservatorio, in which several pieces of music composed by the pupils were performed: uamely, a terzett by M. Quaranta, a duett by M. Eroff, a quartett by M. Fontana, &c.
On	O	_	on	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
19th	O	_	19th	ADJ
September	O	_	September	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
a	O	_	a	DET
concert	O	_	concert	NOUN
was	O	_	be	AUX
given	O	_	give	VERB
by	O	_	by	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
pupils	O	_	pupil	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Conservatorio	B-organization	Q2045972	Conservatorio	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
in	O	_	in	ADP
which	O	_	which	PRON
several	O	_	several	ADJ
pieces	O	_	piece	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
music	O	_	music	NOUN
composed	O	_	compose	VERB
by	O	_	by	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
pupils	O	_	pupil	NOUN
were	O	_	be	AUX
performed	O	_	perform	VERB
:	O	_	:	PUNCT
uamely	O	_	uamely	ADV
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
a	O	_	a	DET
terzett	O	_	terzett	NOUN
by	O	_	by	ADP
M.	B-person	NIL	M.	PROPN
Quaranta	I-person	NIL	Quaranta	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
a	O	_	a	DET
duett	O	_	duett	NOUN
by	O	_	by	ADP
M.	B-person	NIL	M.	PROPN
Eroff	I-person	NIL	Eroff	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
a	O	_	a	DET
quartett	O	_	quartett	NOUN
by	O	_	by	ADP
M.	B-person	NIL	M.	PROPN
Fontana	I-person	NIL	Fontana	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
&	O	_	&	X
c.	O	_	c.	X
