#document_id:TheHarmonicon__1828-001.txt_1782
#document_date:1828
#sent_text:We have had a French opera, at the head of which was M. ‘Nourrit, first tenor of the Academie Royale de Musique.
We	O	_	we	PRON
have	O	_	have	AUX
had	O	_	have	VERB
a	O	_	a	DET
French	O	_	french	ADJ
opera	O	_	opera	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
at	O	_	at	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
head	O	_	head	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
which	O	_	which	PRON
was	O	_	be	AUX
M.	B-person	Q634623	M.	PROPN
‘	I-person	Q634623	‘	PROPN
Nourrit	I-person	Q634623	Nourrit	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
first	O	_	first	ADJ
tenor	O	_	tenor	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Academie	B-organization	Q283339	Academie	PROPN
Royale	I-organization	Q283339	Royale	PROPN
de	I-organization	Q283339	de	X
Musique	I-organization	Q283339	Musique	PROPN
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
