#document_id:DwightSJournalOfMusic__1868-012.txt_749
#document_date:1868
#sent_text:In October Adelina Patti will re-appear in Paris until December, and will then go for two months'td St. Petersburg, returning to the French capital to complete her engagementiat the Italian Opera House up to May, when Adelina Patti will again visit this country for the Royal Italian Opera season.
In	O	_	in	ADP
October	O	_	October	PROPN
Adelina	B-person	Q234166	Adelina	PROPN
Patti	I-person	Q234166	Patti	PROPN
will	O	_	will	AUX
re	O	_	re	VERB
-	O	_	-	VERB
appear	O	_	appear	VERB
in	O	_	in	ADP
Paris	B-city	Q90	Paris	PROPN
until	O	_	until	ADP
December	O	_	December	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
will	O	_	will	AUX
then	O	_	then	ADV
go	O	_	go	VERB
for	O	_	for	ADP
two	O	_	two	NUM
months'td	O	_	months'td	ADP
St.	B-city	Q656	St.	PROPN
Petersburg	I-city	Q656	Petersburg	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
returning	O	_	return	VERB
to	O	_	to	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
French	O	_	french	ADJ
capital	O	_	capital	NOUN
to	O	_	to	PART
complete	O	_	complete	VERB
her	O	_	her	PRON
engagementiat	O	_	engagementiat	NOUN
the	O	_	the	DET
Italian	B-organization	NIL	Italian	PROPN
Opera	I-organization	NIL	Opera	PROPN
House	I-organization	NIL	House	PROPN
up	O	_	up	ADP
to	O	_	to	ADP
May	O	_	May	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
when	O	_	when	SCONJ
Adelina	B-person	Q234166	Adelina	PROPN
Patti	I-person	Q234166	Patti	PROPN
will	O	_	will	AUX
again	O	_	again	ADV
visit	O	_	visit	VERB
this	O	_	this	DET
country	O	_	country	NOUN
for	O	_	for	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Royal	B-organization	Q55018	Royal	PROPN
Italian	I-organization	Q55018	Italian	PROPN
Opera	I-organization	Q55018	Opera	PROPN
season	O	_	season	NOUN
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
