#document_id:TheMusicalTimes__1876-397.txt_1345
#document_date:1876
#sent_text:the Duke of Edinburgh publicly announced that there was no intention, in founding this Institution, of interfering with the operations of the Royal Academy of Music ; and that many other speakers, including Sir Julius Benedict, expressed their intention of supporting the new school as an ally, and not as a rival, of the older one.
the	O	_	the	DET
Duke	B-person	Q158143	Duke	PROPN
of	I-person	Q158143	of	ADP
Edinburgh	I-person	Q158143	Edinburgh	PROPN
publicly	O	_	publicly	ADV
announced	O	_	announce	VERB
that	O	_	that	SCONJ
there	O	_	there	PRON
was	O	_	be	VERB
no	O	_	no	DET
intention	O	_	intention	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
in	O	_	in	ADP
founding	O	_	found	VERB
this	O	_	this	DET
Institution	O	_	Institution	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
of	O	_	of	ADP
interfering	O	_	interfere	VERB
with	O	_	with	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
operations	O	_	operation	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Royal	B-organization	Q1144673	Royal	PROPN
Academy	I-organization	Q1144673	Academy	PROPN
of	I-organization	Q1144673	of	ADP
Music	I-organization	Q1144673	Music	PROPN
;	O	_	;	PUNCT
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
that	O	_	that	SCONJ
many	O	_	many	ADJ
other	O	_	other	ADJ
speakers	O	_	speaker	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
including	O	_	include	VERB
Sir	B-person	Q510435	Sir	PROPN
Julius	I-person	Q510435	Julius	PROPN
Benedict	I-person	Q510435	Benedict	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
expressed	O	_	express	VERB
their	O	_	their	PRON
intention	O	_	intention	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
supporting	O	_	support	VERB
the	O	_	the	DET
new	O	_	new	ADJ
school	O	_	school	NOUN
as	O	_	as	ADP
an	O	_	an	DET
ally	O	_	ally	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
and	O	_	and	CCONJ
not	O	_	not	PART
as	O	_	as	ADP
a	O	_	a	DET
rival	O	_	rival	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
older	O	_	old	ADJ
one	O	_	one	NUM
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
