#document_id:TheMusicalTimes__1876-397.txt_2395
#document_date:1876
#sent_text:the direction of Mr. Carmichael, on Thursday evening, January 27th, in aid of the Building Fund for The Soloists were Miss Madeline Roe, Miss Marie Ternan,
the	O	_	the	DET
direction	O	_	direction	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
Mr.	B-person	NIL	Mr.	PROPN
Carmichael	I-person	NIL	Carmichael	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
on	O	_	on	ADP
Thursday	O	_	Thursday	PROPN
evening	O	_	evening	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
January	O	_	January	PROPN
27th	O	_	27th	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
in	O	_	in	ADP
aid	O	_	aid	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Building	B-organization	NIL	Building	PROPN
Fund	I-organization	NIL	Fund	PROPN
for	I-organization	NIL	for	ADP
The	I-organization	NIL	the	DET
Soloists	I-organization	NIL	Soloists	PROPN
were	O	_	be	AUX
Miss	O	_	Miss	PROPN
Madeline	B-person	NIL	Madeline	PROPN
Roe	I-person	NIL	Roe	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
Miss	B-person	NIL	Miss	PROPN
Marie	I-person	NIL	Marie	PROPN
Ternan	I-person	NIL	Ternan	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
