#document_id:TheMusicalTimes__1873-366.txt_2039
#document_date:1873
#sent_text:Musical Society at Cambridge, in the y Term of 1871, under the direction of Dr. G. M: Garrett.
Musical	B-organization	NIL	Musical	PROPN
Society	I-organization	NIL	Society	PROPN
at	O	_	at	ADP
Cambridge	B-city	Q350	Cambridge	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
in	O	_	in	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
y	O	_	y	ADJ
Term	O	_	Term	PROPN
of	O	_	of	ADP
1871	O	_	1871	NUM
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
under	O	_	under	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
direction	O	_	direction	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
Dr.	B-person	NIL	Dr.	PROPN
G.	I-person	NIL	G.	PROPN
M	I-person	NIL	M	PROPN
:	I-person	NIL	:	PUNCT
Garrett	I-person	NIL	Garrett	PROPN
.	I-person	NIL	.	PUNCT
