#document_id:TheMusicalWorld__1843-029.txt_492
#document_date:1843
#sent_text:Dr. Sponr attended a musical meeting of the Society of British Musicians this morning.— Particulars in our next.
Dr.	B-person	NIL	Dr.	PROPN
Sponr	I-person	NIL	Sponr	PROPN
attended	O	_	attend	VERB
a	O	_	a	DET
musical	O	_	musical	ADJ
meeting	O	_	meeting	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Society	B-organization	Q112578682	Society	PROPN
of	I-organization	Q112578682	of	ADP
British	I-organization	Q112578682	British	PROPN
Musicians	I-organization	Q112578682	Musicians	PROPN
this	O	_	this	DET
morning	O	_	morning	NOUN
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
—	O	_	—	PUNCT
Particulars	O	_	particular	NOUN
in	O	_	in	ADP
our	O	_	our	PRON
next	O	_	next	ADJ
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
