#document_id:TheHarmonicon__1824-016.txt_77
#document_date:1824
#sent_text:, upon hearing of Mr. Viotti’s situation, proposed his undertaking the direction of the Academie Royale de Musique.
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
upon	O	_	upon	SCONJ
hearing	O	_	hearing	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
Mr.	B-person	Q313188	Mr.	PROPN
Viotti	I-person	Q313188	Viotti	PROPN
’s	O	_	’s	PART
situation	O	_	situation	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
proposed	O	_	propose	VERB
his	O	_	his	PRON
undertaking	O	_	undertaking	NOUN
the	O	_	the	DET
direction	O	_	direction	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
the	O	_	the	DET
Academie	B-organization	Q283339	Academie	PROPN
Royale	I-organization	Q283339	Royale	PROPN
de	I-organization	Q283339	de	ADP
Musique	I-organization	Q283339	Musique	PROPN
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
