#document_id:DwightSJournalOfMusic__1875-006.txt_1227
#document_date:1875
#sent_text:The Boylston Clab sang this time under their new Conductor, Mr Geos L. O3scoop, who had been with them only a few weeks, so that the results of his training could hardly yet be very marked.
The	B-organization	NIL	the	DET
Boylston	I-organization	NIL	Boylston	PROPN
Clab	I-organization	NIL	Clab	PROPN
sang	O	_	sing	VERB
this	O	_	this	DET
time	O	_	time	NOUN
under	O	_	under	ADP
their	O	_	their	PRON
new	O	_	new	ADJ
Conductor	O	_	Conductor	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
Mr	B-person	NIL	Mr	PROPN
Geos	I-person	NIL	Geos	PROPN
L.	I-person	NIL	L.	PROPN
O3scoop	I-person	NIL	O3scoop	PROPN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
who	O	_	who	PRON
had	O	_	have	AUX
been	O	_	be	AUX
with	O	_	with	ADP
them	O	_	they	PRON
only	O	_	only	ADV
a	O	_	a	DET
few	O	_	few	ADJ
weeks	O	_	week	NOUN
,	O	_	,	PUNCT
so	O	_	so	SCONJ
that	O	_	that	SCONJ
the	O	_	the	DET
results	O	_	result	NOUN
of	O	_	of	ADP
his	O	_	his	PRON
training	O	_	training	NOUN
could	O	_	could	AUX
hardly	O	_	hardly	ADV
yet	O	_	yet	ADV
be	O	_	be	AUX
very	O	_	very	ADV
marked	O	_	marked	ADJ
.	O	_	.	PUNCT
